question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Pluto is a planet.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
